Finding Aid for the Aron Kuppermann Papers 1946-2012
Caltech Archives
- Talks and Meetings, Series 6.
  - "Quantum dynamics of reactive scattering," International Hot Atom Chemistry Symposium, Brookhaven National Laboratory, September 7-11, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - "A Comparison of exact quantum classical, and semi-classical reaction probabilities," American Chemical Society meeting, Washington, D.C., September 12-17, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - IBM Research Laboratory meeting, San Jose, California, September 16, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Chemical Institute of canada, Symposium on Pulse Radiolysis, Manitoba, Canada, October 25-27, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - "Electron impact and photoelectron spectroscopy," Society for Applied Spectroscopy, Los Angeles, California, December 15, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - NAS-CNPq Chemistry Program meeting, Palo Alto, California, January 20, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - American Chemical Society lecture tour, March 19-24, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    Kuppermann gave talks at Michigan State University, kalamazoo College, Notre Dame University, Grand Valley College, and the University of Michigan
  - "Triplet states in the radiation chemistry of water," Conference on Elementary Processes in Radiation Chemistry, University of Notre Dame, April 4-6, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Xerox Corporation Research Center, Rochester, New York, April 7, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Brazil visit (NAS-CNPq Chemistry Program), April 15-29, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - "Threshold reactions of hydrogen and deuterium atoms," Gordon Research Conference on Chemistry and Physics of Isotopes, Plymouth, New Hampshire, June 26-30, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - "Theory of energy loses of electrons by high energy radiation," Gordon research Conference on Radiation Chemistry, New Hampton, New Hampshire, July 3-7, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Gordon Research Conference on Dynamics of Molecular Collisions, Plymouth, New Hampshire, July 24-28, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Aerospace Corporation Committee on New Gas Lasers, Los Angeles, California, September 20-22, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - "Track structure in the chemical stage," Conference on Physical Mechanisms in radiation Biology, Airlie, Virginia, October 10-15, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Brazil visit (NAS-CNPq Chemistry Program), November 17-28, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Informal seminar, Caltech, December 4, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Winter Colloquium on Quantum Electronics, Snowbird, Utah, January 22-24, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Winter Course in gas Kineticks, Lake Arrowhead, California, February 18-24, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - "Quantum effects in chemical reactions"; "Quantum dynamics of chemical reactions," Indiana University and Ohio state University, February 28-March 1, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - "Description of molecular elastic scattering by central field potentials," American Physical Society meeting, San Diego, California, March 20, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - The Chemical Society, Faraday Division discussion on Molecular Beam Scattering, University College, London, April 16-18, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - "Intermulecular potentials for polyatomic molecules from crossed molecular beam experiments," International Symposium on Molecular Beams, Cannes, France, July 9-12, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, Belgrade, Yugoslavia, July 16-20, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Weizmann Institute of Science visit, Rehovot, Israel, July 29-August 25, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - "Quantum effects in chemical reactions," American Chemical Society Kineticks Symposium, Chicago, illinois, August 27-28, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Brazil visit, September 6-19, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Review of the Atomic Energy Commission Research Program, Argonne National Laboratory, Illinois, November 26-28, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Radiological and Chemical Physics Contractors' meeting, Oak Ridge Laboratory, February 14-15, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Brazil visit (NAS-CNPq Chemistry Program), March 19-30, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - "Quantum dynamics of reactive molecular collisions," Symposium on Mathematical Aspects of Chemical and Biological Problems and Quantum Chemistry, New York, April 10-11, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Air Force Office of Scientific Research meeting, Air Force Academy, Colorado Springs, Colorado, July 10-13, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - "Theories of reactive scattering," Conference on the Dynamics of Molecular Collisions, University of California at Santa Cruz, July 29- August 2, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Laser Induced Chemistry (LIC) meeting, University of California San Diego, December 17-19, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - "The quantum mechanical theory of collision induced dissociation and three body recombination processes using local hyperspherical surface functions," Canadian Symposium on Theoretical Chemistry, Dalhousie University, Halifax, Canada, August 7-12, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - "The generation and properties of a beam of metastable H3 molecules," Air Force Office of Scientific Research meeting, Albuquerque, New Mexico, October 24-26, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - "Hyperspherical coordinates in reactive scattering," Sanibel Symposium on Atomic, Molecular and Solid State Theory, St. Augustine, Florida, March 18-23, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - "Hyperspherical coordinates," NATO Advanced Research Workshop on The Theory of Chemical Reaction Dynamics, Orsay, France, June 17-30, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Air Force Office of Scientific Research meeting on Surface Chemistry, Dayton, Ohio, November 4-6, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - "Computational chemical dynamics," Research Directors Conference, Caltech, February 4-5, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Air Force Office of Scientific Research meeting on Molecular Dynamics, Bedford, Massachusettes, October 14-17, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Orientation seminar for new graduate students, Caltech, October 21, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - National Science Foundation meeting, washington, D.C., December 4-5, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    Regarding concurrent supercomputer.
  - "Caltech Hypercube," Research Directors Conference, Caltech, February 11, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - GenCorp visit, Caltech, February 25, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    Includes Kuppermann's report titled "Tetrahydrogene" submitted to the Air Force Rocket Propulsion Laboratory (AFRPL TR-86-103) dated January 1987.
  - "Ab initio calculation of state to state reactive scattering using hyperspherical coordinates," University of Illinois at Chicago, March 9-10, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - "Theoretical studies of the lifetime of metastable trihydrogen and tetrahydrogene," High Energy Density Matter Conference, Air Force Rocket Propulsion Laboratory, Washington, D.C., May 11-13, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - "The Spectroscopy and Dynamics of metastable neutral H3 molecule," Los Angeles Community College, Los Angeles, California, May 15, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - "Quantum reaction dynamics," International Congress of Pure and Applied Chemistry, Sofia, Bulgaria, July 13-18, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - "Accurate integral and differential, inelastic cross sections and resonance lifetimes for electron hydrogene atom scattering," International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, Brighton, England, July 22-28, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - "Theoretical and experimental studies of the properties and lifetime of metastable trihydrogen," High Energy Density Matter Conference, Air Force Office of Scientific Research, Newport Beach, California, February 28-March 2, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - "Accurate quantum mechanical calculations of state to state reaction cross sections," Seminar at the University of California, Los Angeles, April 18, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation Rice University visit, Houston, Texas, July 6-7, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - National Institute of health Special Study Section (SSS-1), Cornell University site visit, Ithaca, New York, July 12-14, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - "Accurate Ab initio calculation of reaction cross sections using hyperspherical coordinates," International Congress on Quantum Chemistry, Jerusalem, Israel, August 29-31, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - World Bank meeting, Washington, D.C., September 5-9, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - "Teoria de espalhamento de rea?oes químicas," Latin American School of Theoretical Chemistry, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, September 10-16, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    Lecture notes in Portuguese.
  - Interamerican Development Bank (IDB) Project meeting, University of São Paulo, Brazil, October 31- November 4, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Parallel Concurent Supercomputing meeting, Albuquerque, New Mexico, January 23-25, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - "The use of supercomputers in quantum mechanical reactive scattering calculations," Supercomputing Conference and User Services Group meeting, Kirtland Air Force Base, New Mexico, February 7-9, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - "Experimental and theoretical studies of the properties of trihydrogen," High Energy Density Materials Contractors Conference, New Orleans, Louisiana, March 12-15, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - "Calculations of scattering and bound rovibrational states of triatomic using an hyperspherical propagation method," Sanibel Simposia, St. Augustine, Florida, April 4-9, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Orientation seminar for new graduate students, Caltech, October 17, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Office of Naval research Workshop on Highly Parallel Computing for Scientific Problems, Princeton, New Jersey, January 7-9, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - National Science Foundation meeting, Washington, D.C., March 20-22, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    Folder contains travel itinerary only.
  - "Three dimentional reactive scattering with parallel supercomputers," Conference on Quantum Theory of Reactive Scattering, Cambridge, England, March 25-27, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - "Chemical reaction dynamics," Intel Partners' meeting, Caltech, May 31, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    Folder also contains material from the June 28, 1990 meeting.
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil, June 1-19, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - "Hyperspherical reactive scattering on a hypercube supercomputer," Centre Européen de Calcul Atomique et Moléculaire (CECAM) Workshop, Meudon, France, July 16-August 3, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - "Uso de supercomputadores paralelos na teoria quantica de rea?oes químicas," University of São Paulo, Brazil, August 10-26, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - "Accurate quantum reactive scattering on parallel computers using hyperspherical coordinates," Parallel Computing for Chemical Reactivity meeting, Perugia, Italy, August 29-September 2, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - "The Intel Delta System and the Concurrent Supercomputing Consortium," Caltech, December 10, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - World Bank Mission, Mexico City, Mexico, January 22-February 8, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Gigabit Testbed Workshop, Bethesda, Maryland, February 12-15, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - "The use of sequential and parallel supercomputer architectures in chemistry," H.C. Orsted institute, Copenhagen, Denmark, March 9-16, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - "Quantum reaction dynamics and the potential of massively parallel computers," Harvard University, May 7-8, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Caltech Associates' presentation, May 30, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - World Bank Mission to Mexico, Mexico City, Mexico, June 16-29, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    Folder contains only travel itinerary.
  - International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, Brisbane, Australia, July 7-31, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil, August 23-September 8, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Eastman Kodak/Datatape meeting, Caltech, October 15, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - "Hyperspherical coordinates in many body collision processes," Group seminar, Caltech, October 30, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - "Quantum chemical reaction dynamics," Gigabit Testbed meeting, Washington, D.C., November 6, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - "Quantum chemical reaction dynamics," Gigabit Testbed meeting, La Jolla, California, January 13-15, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - World Bank Mission, Mexico City, Mexico, January 19-25, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - "Accurate calculation of the cross sections and rates of chemical reactions from first quantum mechanical principles using massively parallel computers," Research Directors Conference, Caltech, February 6-7, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - "Ab initio quantum mechanic calculation of the cross sections and rates of chemical reactions," Concurrent Supercomputing Consortium Workshop, Caltech, February 11-12, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - National Science Foundation Workshop on Supercomputer Centers, Houston, Texas, March 6-8, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - "The Intel Touchstone Delta System: A new computational tool for large scale applications," San Diego Supercomputer Center (SDSC) Steering Committee meeting, San Diego, California, March 9, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - "The effect of conical interactions and the geometric phase on chemical reactions," Arrhenius Rate Symposium, Jerusalem, Israel, April 5-10, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - "The molecular Bohm-Aharonov effect in chemical reaction cross sections," Orsay, France, May 12, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - "Thefuture of theoretical quantum reaction dynamics," Laboratoire Aimé-Cotton (LAC), Paris, France, May 19, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - "The effect of conical interactions on chemical reaction cross sections," Observatoire de Paris, France, June 4, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - "O futurao da dinâmica quãntica das rea?óes químics e a supercomputa?ão paralela," Universidad Federal de Pernambuco (UFPE), Recife, Brazil, August 25, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - "Hyperspherical coordinates for N- particle analysis," Group seminar, Caltech, October 21, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - "Symmetrized hyperspherical coordinates for N-Particle systems," NATO Advanced Workshop, Assisi, Italy, November 20-25, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - "A New experimentally observed phenomenon in reaction dynamics" the geometric phase effect," University of California, Irvine, January 5, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - World Bank Mission to Mexico, Mexico City, Mexico, February 22-27, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - "Opportunities and challenges of high performance computing in chemistry," National Institute of Health Workshop, Bethesda, Maryland, March 8-10, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil, April 10-22, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - "The use of massively parallel computer on quantum mechanical reactive scattering," Ohio State University, Columbus, Ohio, June 1-3, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - "The geometric phase shows up in chemical reactions," Conference on the Dynamics of Molecular Collisions, Helen, Georgia, June 5-10, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - "Dinamica das rea?óes químicas presente e futuro," Sociedada Brasileira para o Progresso da ciência, Recife, Brazil, July 8-August 11, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - New student orientation camp, Catalina Island, California, September 22-24, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - "Investments in science and technology," University of São Paulo; and, "manifesta?ão de fase geométrica (de Berry) nas rea?ões químicas," Catholic University of Rio, Brazil, October 8-16, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - "Effect of the geometric (Berry) phase on quantum reaction dynamics," University of california, Irvine, November 12, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - "The effect of the geometric (Berry) phase on the dynamics of chemical reactions," Annual Western States Mathematical Physics meeting, Caltech, February 28, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - "Quantum resonances in the reaction of F atoms with HD molecules," Symposium on Chemical Dynamics in the Gas Phase, San Diego, California, March 14-17, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - "Quantum reaction dynamics and superlinear speedup," San Diego Supercomputer Center (SDSC) Steering Committee meeting, San Diego, California, March 22, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - "The use of massively parallel computer in quantum mechanical reactive scattering," High Performance Computing Symposium, San Diego, California, April 12, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - "The effect of the geometric (Berry) phase in chemical reactions," American Physical Society meeting, Washington, D.C., April 21, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - "The geometric phase: A new quantum mechanical principle governing the dynamics of chemical reactions," Georgetown University, Washington, D.C., April 22, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - "The effect of the geometric phase in chemical reaction cross sections," Rutgers University, New Jersey, April 26, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - "Quantum chemical reaction dynamics with massively parallel high performance computers", June 21, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - "Asymmetrized system of hyperspherical coordinates for tetra atomic reactions," Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics, Cambridge, Massachusettes, June 29 - July 3, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - "Adiabatic and diabatic representation for reactive scattering calculations," Argonne National Laboratory Workshop, Chicago, Illinois, July 19-24, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - "Quantum reaction dynamics with massively parallel computers," American chemical Society Symposium on Nonadiabatic Dynamics, Washington, D.C., August 20-26, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - San Diego Supercomputer Center (SDSC) Executive Committee meeting, San Diego, California, September 12-13, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Orientation seminar for new graduate students, Caltech, October 4, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Corporation for National Research Initiatives CNRI) Gigabit Testbed meeting, Reston, Virginia, November 1-4, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Pasadena Workshop on System Software and Tools for High Performance Computing Environment, Jet propulsion Laboratory, January 10-12, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - "Effect of the geometric phase on differential and integral reaction cross sections," University of Nevada, Las Vegas, February 1-2, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - "Quantum mechanical reactive scattering using massively parallel high performance computers," Louisiana State University, Baton Rouge, February 19-25, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Martin Karplus 65th Birthday Symposium, Harvard University, Cambridge, March 17-19, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Presentation for Intel representatives, Caltech, April 5, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - "Hyperspherical coordinates in reactive scattering theory," Advanced Research Workshop on New Methods in Quantum Theory, Halkidiki, Greece, May 11-12, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - San Diego Supercomputer Center (SDSC) Executive and Steering Committee meeting, San Diego, California, June 12, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Center for Advanced Computing Research (CACR) retreat, Fallbrock, California, June 13, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil, June 16-28, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - "The quantitative predictions of a pronounced ? reactive scattering resonance," Conference on Reaction Dynamicd, University of Nottingham, England, August 28 - September 3, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - "A Strong geometric phase resonance ?" European Workshop on Molecular Spectroscopy photon Induced Dynamics, Trinity College, Oxford, England, September 3-7, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - "Time decay and lifetime analysis of reactive scattering," Group seminar, Caltech, October 24, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - "The geometric phase and resonances in quantum reaction dynamics," University of Oklahoma, Norman, April 24-26, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - World Bank meeting, Washington, D.C., April 29 - May 2, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - American Physical Society meeting, Indianapolis, Indiana, May 2-5, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Brazil visit, June 12 - July 5, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - "Time dependent wave packet analysis of time dependent reactive scattering calculations," European Conference on Dynamics of Molecular Collision (MOLEC XI), Copenhagen, Denmark, September 1-6, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Center for Advanced Computing Research (CACR) retreat, Lake Arrowhead, California, October 7, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - "The role of San Diego Supercomputer Center Steering Committee," Caltech, October 22-23, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    Part of the National Partnership for Advanced Computational Infrastructure (NPACI) site visit.
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil, November 8-20, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Modern trends in Chemical Dynamics Symposium, Taipei, Taiwan, December 6-13, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - World Bank Mission to Mexico, Mexico City, February 23-28, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil, March 15-30, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil, April 19- May 5, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - World Bank Mission to China, June 2-21, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - "Resonances in atom-diatom chemical reactions," The Institute for Theoretical Atomic and Molecular Physics (ITAMP) Workshop, Cambridge, Massachusettes, July 10-12, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - "The geometric phase effect formalism in tetraatomic chemical reactions," Quantum Reactive Scattering Workshop, Telluride Summer Research Center, Telluride, Colorado, July 28 - August 1, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - World Bank Mission to Mexico, Mexico City, April 13-20, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - "An Accurate quantum Monte Carlo potential energy surface for H3 and some of its scattering properties," The Royal Society of Chemistry, University of St. Andrews, Scitland, UK, July 1-3, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - World Bank Mission to Chile and Brazil, November 14 - December 2, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - World Bank Mission to Chile, January 23-30, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Boys Rahman lecture tour, England, April 15 - May 4, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - World Bank Mission to Brazil, May 7-21, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - "Bohmian view of quantum reaction dynamics," Workshop on Quantum reaction Scattering, University of Perugia, Italy, June 23 - July 16, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - "A Bohmian view of reaction dynamics," Stanford University, October 7, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - The National Partnership for Advanced Computational Infrastructure (NPACI) meeting, San Diego, California, February 8-11, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - "Hyperspherical coordinates in the quantum reactive scattering of three and four atom systems," Summer School on Dynamics of Molecular Collisions, Weizmann Institute of Science, Rehovot, Israel, September 11-15, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - "A Bohmian view of quantum reaction dynamics," Conference on Dynamics of Molecular Collisions (MOLEC 2000), Jerusalem ,Israel, September 17-22, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Pasadena Workshop on Quantum Reaction Dynamics, Caltech, January 10-13, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - "The importance of the geometric phase for chemical reactions," Sanibel Symposium, University of Florida, St. Augistine, February 23-26, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - The National Partnership for Advanced Computational Infrastructure (NPACI) meeting, San Diego, California, February 27-28, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - The National Partnership for Advanced Computational Infrastructure (NPACI) retreat, Carlsbad, California, June 14-16, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - The National Partnership for Advanced Computational Infrastructure (NPACI) Executive Committee meeting, La Jolla, California, October 31 - November 2, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - The National Partnership for Advanced Computational Infrastructure (NPACI) Executive Committee meeting, Houston, Texas, January 23-26, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - World Bank Mission to Mexico, Mexico City, January 28 - February 2, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 33)